# Yvette Zuniga

(469) 789-4047 | yvettezuniga5@gmail.com | Dallas, TX linkedin.com/in/yvette-zuniga-286a00239

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Recent graduate with 460+ training hours and experience developing full stack Java applications. Excited to apply my acquired skills and attain a career that will allow me the opportunity to excel in software development as well as highlight my passion for implementing creative solutions.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

W3Schools JavaScript Certification (in progress; expected date of completion 10/2022)

- Java
- Spring Data JPA
- Unit Testing (JUnit, Mockito)
- JavaScript
- Spring Security (JWT)
- HTML
- Bootstrap
- SOLID OOP Principles
- CSS
- REST API's

- Dependencies Injection
- Spring Boot
- SQL
- Git

#### **EDUCATION**

University of North Texas at Dallas | Dallas, TX | August 2019- May 2022

- Bachelor of Liberal Arts and Sciences, Information Technology
- Major GPA: 3.9/4.0

#### **Relevant Coursework**

- Computer Science I & II learned objectoriented programming with Java
- Intro to Database Systems Design Created relational databases using SQL and MySQL
- Data Structures and Algorithms Attained the ability to write efficient programs
- Software Engineering Studied the project life cycle and the waterfall agile process

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**Generation Junior Full Stack Java Developer Program** | Remote | August 2022- December 2022 *Training Participant (in progress)* 

- Participating in a 16-week, 460+ hour Junior Full Stack Java Developer program that emphasizes hands-on practical application
- Learning and deploying the technologies involved in creating full stack web applications with Java using Spring Boot Framework, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3
- Implementing basic unit tests and deploying the application to Heroku

**Inmar Inc.** | Grand Prairie, TX | June 2019-August 2019 *Processor (Scanner)* 

- Processed returns of over 2,000 medical products
- Handled the disposal of medical products based on the client's protocol
- Verified accuracy of product information logged in the company's database